<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Júlio&#39;s Page</title>
    <link>https://juliobguedes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Júlio&#39;s Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 19:49:39 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://juliobguedes.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tormenta Spellbook</title>
      <link>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/tormenta-spellbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 19:49:39 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/tormenta-spellbook/</guid>
      <description>Tormenta is a brazilian RPG based on D&amp;amp;D (Open Game License was a bless) very similar to D&amp;amp;D3.5 but with a totally different and new scene. The spells and feats are very similar, having a few differences in the mechanics and rules.
  As a RPG player and master, a great part of the time playing was devoted to search stuff in the books during the game. In TormentaRPG, we have a lot of them, and had even more in D&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MusicHub</title>
      <link>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/musichub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 19:49:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/musichub/</guid>
      <description>Easy Stock is a web application developed in Angular.js. The application was made as a part of the Informational Systems class, taught by Melina Mongiovi.
Main user stories:
 As an user, I would like to add an artist to the system. In a text box, the user can add the artist info and add him to the system.  The artist name is required, but its image is optional; Two different artists can not have the same name;  As an user, I would like to add a song to the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Stock</title>
      <link>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/easystock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 19:49:26 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/easystock/</guid>
      <description>Easy Stock is a web application developed in Angular.js, Spring-boot and PostgreSQL. The application was made as a part of the Informational Systems class, taught by Melina Mongiovi.
During the class, we learned code patterns and, in the end of the class, we had to develop (and fix) a project given by Melina. The project had 13 main user stories and 3 aditional user stories:
Main user stories:
 As an admin, I would like to have the system persisting all the data; As an admin, I would like to login in the system to have access to all the admin funcionalities; As an admin, I would like to access the system through a link; I, as a client, would like to consult the disponibility and price of each product of the supermarket without the need of being logged in; As an admin, I would like to order the products and the record of sales according to their important information (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Libratizar</title>
      <link>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/libratizar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 19:49:20 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/libratizar/</guid>
      <description>Libratizar is a Startup from Campina Grande with focus in inclusive education. Our main proposal is that education should be to everyone.
The Libratizar started in Campina Grande in the 14th FETECh, organized by the Parque Tecnológico/PB (PaqTecPB) and the Incubadora Tecnológica de Campina Grande (ITCG), during the 1st FETECh Hackathon. I made my subscription to the event with 2 other friends, Renan and Mariana, but the teams were drawn in the beginning of the competition, revealed with the theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualizations</title>
      <link>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/datavis1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 10:55:34 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliobguedes.github.io/post/datavis1/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone!
My data visualization page was created using Hugo to host a series of visualizations made in d3.js and Vega Lite, a d3 compiler. All of them were made in the DataVis class @ UFCG, taught by Nazareno Andrade, with the purpose to learn d3.js, the tecniques and theory about visualizations.
In each post, I&amp;rsquo;ll present the same guide made by Nazareno that lead me to create the visualizations. I a few of them I made use of Python to modify the original data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>